<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="exerciseTitles">
        <tem>Warm-up</tem>
        <item>Lateral raise</item>
        <item>Lat pulldown</item>
        <item>Cable rows</item>
        <item>Tricep pushdowns</item>
        <item>Crunch</item>
        <item>Back extensions</item>
        <item>Cardio trainings</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="exerciseTexts">
        <item>
            Some warm-up exercises. It is important to warming-up and
            stretch every muscle which will be burden.
        </item>
        <item>
            The lateral raise with dumbbells is an effective exercise for developing the deltoids,
            and is performed by extending the arm to the side of the body with the elbow extended.
        </item>
        <item>
            The lat pulldown works the major muscles in the back and also the biceps in the arms.
            It's a good exercise to progress up to doing pull ups as it develops strength in the back and arms,
            so its ideal for beginners.
        </item>
        <item>
            Seated cable rows are a great way to work the back muscles. Varying the width of your hands
            focuses the intensity on different areas of the back. Because it's a pulling exercise you
            are also working your biceps.
        </item>
        <item>
            Tricep pushdowns isolate the tricep muscles and are usually done at the tail end of a workout
            to give the triceps a real pump. It's a very easy exercise to perform and is ideal for beginners
            to weight training.
        </item>
        <item>
            The standard abdominal crunch exercise targets the stomach muscles. The crunch is a safe
            and effective exercise that is great for beginners to help develop strong abdominal muscles.
        </item>
        <item>
            Back extensions are also known as hyperextensions. It's an exercise that works the lower
            back and also the buttocks and hamstrings.
        </item>
        <item>
            Training for pussy-man, which doesn't want to kick somebody's ass on street, only likes pedalling
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>